Guide to the Steele Ranch Records, 1855-1973
Department of Special Collections
Steele Ranch Records,
1855-1973
Special Collections M0237
Steele Ranch.
48.5 linear ft.
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections and University Archives.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
None.
Provenance
Gift of Mrs. Catherine Baumgarten Steele, 1972.
Scope and Content
The collection is a compilation of ranch papers from the Steele Ranches of San Mateo County, California. The papers include financial papers, legal papers, photographs, maps, miscellaneous background notes written by Mrs. Catherine Steele. The collection covers over 100 years of ranching in California.
Some Steel Ranch material was included in the earlier gift from Mrs Steele which is still part of the Gen. Frederick Steele Papers. (M0191) See correspondence, photographs, research notes, clippings and other miscellaney.
ST May 1980.
Description of Series
- Series A: CORRESPONDENCE, 1855-1973 (Box 1-4)
- Series B: FINANCIAL PAPERS (Box 5 - 42)
- Series C: INSURANCE PAPERS (Box 43 - 44)
- Series D: LEGAL PAPERS (Box 45 - 46)
- Series E: PHOTOGRAPHS (Box 47 - 56)
- Series F: MISCELLANEOUS (Box 57 - 59)
- Series G: BOOKS & MAGAZINES (Box 60 - 63)
- Series H: MAPS (Box 64 - 65)
- Series I: NEWSCLIPPINGS & NEWSPAPERS (Box 66 - 70)
- Series J: PAMPHLETS (Box 71)
- Series K: NON-ORIGINAL MATERIAL (XEROXES, REPRODUCTIONS, ETC.) (Box 72)
- Series L: CATHERINE STEELE'S MANUSCRIPT NOTES (Box 73 - 79)
- Series M: C. STEELE'S TYPESCRIPT NOTES (Box 80 - 82)
NAME ABBREVIATIONS KEY - (page 110 - 117 of guide)
CONTAINER LIST
- SERIES A. CORRESPONDENCE: 1855-1973
  - Correspondence, 1855-1868 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 1. 1855, Sept. 4.S.F., Ca. G.S. to Ed re: first impressions of Calif. - prospects for making money., A.L.S.
    - 2. 1856, Mar. 31.Rock Island, Ill. N.C. Moffett to Edgar., A.L.S.
    - 3. 1857, Dec. 16.S.F., Ca. G. Richards to Steeles., A.L.S
    - 4. 1858, Oct. 25.Rockport. - Barnum? to Emiline., A.L.S
    - 5. 1861, Mar. 10.N.P. Smith Steele to Brother., A.L.S.
    - 6. 1861, July 23.S.F., Ca. T.H. Hatch & Co. to E.W.S., A.L.S.
    - 7. 1861, Aug. 14.S.F., Ca. T.H. Hatch & Co. to E.W.S., A.L.S.
    - 8. 1862, July 24.Greenwood. Anna to Brother., A.L.S.
    - 9. 1862, Oct. 6.Sebastopol. E.W.S.* to Charley re: cattle., A.L.S.
    - 10. Same as # 9.
    - 11. 1862, Oct. 6.Petaluma. G.S. to Charley re: ranching - price of 2 year old heifers., A.L.S.
    - 12. 1862, Oct. 8.S.F., [Ca.]. Chas. H. Willson to E.W.S.* and Horace Gushee re: financial matters., A.L.S.
    - 13. 1862, Oct. 11.Sebastopol. H. Gushee to C.H. Wilson [Willson] re: cattle., A.L.S.
    - 14. 1862, Oct. 14.Petaluma. Horace Gushee to Willson re: cattle., A.L.S.
    - 15. 1862, Oct. 18.Sebastopol. E. Newburgh to Mr. Gushee re: cattle., A.L.S.
    - 16. 1862, Oct. 19.Pescadero. R.E.S. to Sir re: cattle., A.L.S.
    - 17. 1862, Nov. 11.Petaluma. E.W.S.* to Charley re: cattle., A.L.S.
    - 18. 1862, Nov. 11.Petaluma. G.S. to Charley re: financial matters., A.L.S.
    - 19. 1862, Nov. 16.Pescadero. Horace Gushee to Willson re: ranch and cattle., A.L.S.
    - 20. 1862, Dec. 7.Pescadero. I.C.S. to Friend re: dairy construction at Pigeon Point and finances., A.L.S.
    - 21. 1862, Dec. 11.Big Valley. D.B. (?) Stanard to R.E.S., A.L.S.
    - 22. 1862, Dec. 25.Seventeen Mile House. E.W.S.* to H. Gushee and C.H. Willson re: stock auction., A.L.S.
    - 23. 1863, Jan. 8.White House. E.W.S.* to Charley., A.L.S.
    - 24. 1863, Jan. 11.Gazos Ranch. E.W.S.* to Charley re: finances and ranching., A.L.S.
    - 25. 1863, Jan. 14.Pescadero. I.C.S. to Friend re: finances., A.L.S.
    - 26. 1863, Jan. 29.Gazos Rancho. E.W.S.* to Charley re: settlers on the ranch - rent matters., A.L.S.
    - 26a. 1863, Jan. 29The Pocket/E.W.S. to Charley re: settlers & finances
    - 27. 1863, Feb. 7.The Pocket (?). E.W.S.* to Charley re: finances., A.L.S.
    - 28. 1863, Feb. 27.Muddy Hollow. J.W. Seelye to E.W.S.* re: dairying., A.L.S.
    - 29. 1863, April 11.Punta Reyes. E.S. John to Edgar re: dairying., A.L.S.
    - 30. 1863, July 31.S.F., [Ca.]. A. Elder to E.W.S.* re: finances., A.L.S.
    - 31. 1863, Aug. 27. _____(?). E.S. John (?) to Ed., A.L.S.
    - 32. 1863, Dec. 10.Punta Reyes. E.S. John to Edgar re: ranching., A.L.S.
    - 33. 1864, Jan. 13.Punta Reyes. E.S. to Ed re: dairying., A.L.S.
    - 34. 1864, Jan. 18.San Rafael. G.S. to Brother., A.L.S.
    - 35. 1864, Jan. 18.Ridgeville. J.W. Seelye to Steele., A.L.S.
    - 36. 1864, Jan. 21.New York. A.J. Davis (Moral Police Fraternity) to Brother., A.L.S.
    - 37. 1864, Mar. 9.San Rafael. G.S. to Brother., A.L.S.
    - 38. 1864, Mar. 24.Green Oak Ranch. Unknown to Niece., A.L.
    - 39. 1866, Jan. 9.S.F., Ca. Campbell, Fox & Campbell to Steele Brothers., A.L.S.
    - 40. 1866, Feb. 8.Pescadero. James Wilson to Mr. Steele re: cheese and cattle., A.L.S.
    - 41. 1866, April 3.San Rafael. G.S. to Brother Ed., A.L.S.
    - 42. 1866, Sept. 29.Santa Cruz. Joseph H. _____? to W.W. Waddell re: legal matters., A.L.S.
    - 43. 1867, Jan. 22.S.F., Ca. _____? to Friend., A.L.S.
    - 44. 1867, April 12.S.F., Ca. T.H. Hatch & Co. to I.C.S. re: the cheese trade.
    - 45. 1867, April 27.S.F., Ca. T.H. Hatch & Co. to E.W.S.* re: cheese trade., A.L.S.
    - 46. 1867, Dec. 18.N.P. E.E. Moore (?) to Brother., A.L.S.
    - 47. 1868, Feb. 3.N.P. Moses Chinmark to E.S., A.L.S.
    - 48. 1868, April 2.New York. Willson, Watrous & Co. (C.W.) to Ed., A.L.
    - 49. 1868, April 16.Santa Cruz, Ca. Ella Steele to Cousin., A.L.S.
    - 50. 1868, May 7.S.F., Ca. Ella to Aunt Em., A.L.S.
    - 51. 1868, May 25.Oak Knoll. G.S. to Brother., A.L.S.
    - 52. 1868, June 1.Chattanouga. (Henry) R. Stanley to _____?., A.L.S.
    - 53. 1868, June 5.Pescadero, Ca. Henry Stanley to Edgar re: ranching - hogs., A.L.S.
    - 54. 1868, June 18. _____?Half Way House. _____? Olden(?) to Steele Bros. re: ranching - cattle brands., A.L.S.
    - 55. 1868, June 23.San Jose, Ca. J.H. Flickinger to E.W.S., A.L.S.
    - 56. 1868, July22.Carmel. _____? to Edgar., A.L.S.
    - 57. 1868, Sept. 12.Amherst. _____? to husband., A.L.S.
    - 58. 1868, Oct. 19.Green Oaks. Effie to Uncle Edgar., A.L.S.
    - 59. 1868, Oct. 31.Point New Year. I.C.S. to Brother., A.L.S.
    - 60. 1868, Dec. 10.San Rafael. G.S. to Brother., A.L.S.
  - Correspondence, 1869-1874 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 1. 1869, Jan. 23.Green Oaks, Calif. I.C.S. to Brother., A.L.S.
    - 2. 1869, Mar. 26.San Mateo, Calif. Mrs. J.I.A. Tilton (?) to Mr. Steele., A.L.S.
    - 3. 1869, April 17.Salinas, Ca. F. Ramsay to E.W.S.*, A.L.S.
    - 4. 1869, May 7.S.F., Ca. T.H. Hatch & Co. to E.W.S.*, A.L.S.
    - 5. Same as #4.
    - 6. 1869, May 18.S.F., Ca. T.H.Hatch & Co. to E.W.S.*, A.L.S.
    - 7. 1869, May 20.Santa Cruz, Ca. Ella to Folkses., A.L.S.
    - 8. 1869, May 25.S.F., Ca. T.H. Hatch & Co. to E.W.S.* re: the cheese trade., A.L.S.
    - 9. 1869, June 19.Oak Knoll. E.W.S.* to Brother re: purchasing a dairy., A.L.S.
    - 10. 1869. Aug. 16.S.F., Ca. S.P. Crittenden to E.W.S.*, A.L.S.
    - 11. 1869, Nov. 5.S.F., Ca. Henri Fehn (?) to (Steele) Bros. re: cheese., A.L.S.
    - 12. 1869, Dec. 6.San Luis Obispo, Ca. O.N.S. to Uncle Edgar., A.L.S.
    - 13. N.D. 187_.Santa Rosa, Ca. W.E. McConnell to _____?, A.L.S.
    - 14. N.D. 187_.Kellogg, Ca. Knight's Valley House (C.F.H.) to _____? frag., A.L.
    - 15. 1870, Feb. 4.Sacramento, Ca. _____? to Wife., A.L.S.
    - 16. 1870, July 5.S.F., Ca. T.H. Hatch & Co. to I.C.S., A.L.S.
    - 17. 1870, July 26.New Years Gulch. O.N.S. to Uncle Ike re: supplies., A.L.S.
    - 18. 1870, Aug. 4.S.F., Ca. T.H. Hatch & Co. to I.C.S., A.L.S.
    - 19. 1870, Aug. 20.S.F., Ca. A. Elder to Fred re: finances., A.L.S.
    - 20. 1870, Oct. 3.Petaluma, Ca. S. _(?) Elder to Friend., A.L.S.
    - 21. 1870, Nov. 25.Point New Years. F.N.S. to Will., A.L.S.
    - 22. 1870, Dec. 22.S.F., Ca. T.H. Hatch & Co. (E.) to I.C.S., A.L.S.
    - 23. 1871, Jan. 12.S.F., Ca. T.H. Hatch & Co. (A.S.) to I.C.S., A.L.S.
    - 24. 1871, Feb.S.F., Ca. T.H. Hatch & Co. to Steele Bros. re: cheese., A.L.S.
    - 25. 1871, Feb. 13.S.F., Ca. T.H. Hatch & Co. to Steele Bros. re: cheese., A.L.S.
    - 26. Same as # 25.
    - 27. 1871, March 6.S.F., Ca. T.H. Hatch & Co. to Steele Bros. re: cheese., A.L.S.
    - 28. 1871, March 10.S.F., Ca. T.H. Hatch & Co. re: dairying - cheese., A.L.S.
    - 29. 1871, March 17.S.F., Ca. T.H. Hatch & Co. to Steele Bros. re: cheese., A.L.S.
    - 30. 1871, April 3.S.F., Ca. T.H. Hatch & Co. to I.C.S. re: cheese., A.L.S.
    - 31. 1871, April 10.S.F., Ca. T.H. Hatch & Co. to Steele Bros. re: cheese., A.L.S.
    - 32. 1871, July 7.San L[uis Obispo], Ca. Finney(?) to Unknown., A.L.S.
    - 33. 1871, Sept. 12.Corral de Piedra Ranch House. Unknown to Fred re: dairying & financial matters., A.L.
    - 34. 1872, N.D.S.F., Ca. [Stuart & Elder] to Unknown re: cheese., A.N.
    - 35. 1872, Aug. 7.San Jose, Ca. C. Burrel to I.C.S., A.L.S.
    - 36. 1872, Aug. 13.S.F., Ca. Stuart & Elder to Steele Bros., A.L.S.
    - 37. 1872, Aug. 16.S.F., Ca. Stuart & Elder to I.C.S. re: cheese & finances., A.L.S.
    - 38. 1872, Aug. 17.S.F., Ca. Stuart & Elder to I.C.S. re: finances., A.L.S.
    - 39. 1872, Sept. 1.E.E. Moore to Brother., A.L.S.
    - 40. 1872, Sept. 3.Beverly. A.H_____(?) to Brother., A.L.S.
    - 41. 1872, Oct. 7.S.F., Ca. Will to E.W.S. re: finances., A.L.S.
    - 42. 1872, Oct. 8.Pescadero, Ca. A. Weeks to Steele., A.N.S.
    - 43. 1872, Oct. 8.S.F., Ca. Stuart & Elder to E.W.S. re: finances., A.L.S.
    - 44. 1873, April 7.Pescadero, Ca. J. Garretson to I.C.S., A.L.S.
    - 45. 1873, May 11.S.F., Ca. Stuart & Elder to I.C.S., A.L.S.
    - 46. 1873, Aug. 11.S.F., Ca. Stuart & Elder to I.C.S., A.L.S.
    - 47. 1873, Aug. 13.San Jose, Ca. C. Burrel to I.C.S., A.L.S.
    - 48. 1873, Aug. 29.S.F., Ca. [Stuart & Elder] to Steele re: finances., A.L.S.
    - 49. 1873, Nov. 12.Monterey, Ca. Lambert & Brother to I.C.S., A.L.S.
    - 50. 1874, Jan. 10.Santa Cruz, Ca. Lucien Heath to I.C.S. re: finances., A.L.S.
    - 51. 1874, Feb. 16.Santa Cruz, Ca. Lucien Health to I.C.S., A.L.S.
    - 52. 1874, Mar. 21.S.F., Ca. Stuart & Elder to I.C.S., A.L.S.
  - Correspondence from I.C. Steele contained in one bound volume, 1878 - 1880. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1875-1896 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 1. 1875, Jan. 12.S.F., Ca. E.W.S.* to Brother re: finances., A.L.S.
    - 2. 1875, Jan. 21.N.P. E.W.S.* to Brother re: finances., A.L.S.
    - 3. 1875, Feb. 1.S.F., Ca. Unknown to Brother re: finances. frag., A.L.
    - 4. 1875, June 28.Brooklyn, Ca. J.M. Patterson to Steele Bros. re: cattle., A.L.S.
    - 5. 1875, Aug.S.F., Ca. W.H. Baxter to Sir & Bro., A.L.S.
    - 6. 1875, Sept. 14.S.F., Ca. Steele, Elder & Co. to I.C.S. re: finances., A.L.S.
    - 7. 1875, Nov. 14.Berlin Heights, O. Hudson Tuttle to S.J. Finney., A.L.S.
    - 8. 1875, Dec. 2.S.F., Ca. A. Elder to I.C.S., A.L.S.
    - 9. 1875, Dec. 27.S.F., Ca. E.W.S.* to Brother re: finances., A.L.S.
    - 10. 1876, Jan. 29.N.P. E.W.S.* to Brother., A.L.S.
    - 11. 1876, Mar. 25.S.F., Ca. G.S. to Brother re: finances., A.L.S.
    - 12. 1876, Mar. 28.S.F., Ca. Unknown to Brother. frag. re: finances., A.L.
    - 13. 1876, July 22.Pescadero, Ca. I.C.S. to Peseadero Grange., A.L.S.
    - 14. 1876, July 22.Pescadero, Ca. I.C.S. to the Patrons of the Pescadero Grange., A.L.S.
    - 15. 1876, Aug. 29.San Luis Obispo, Ca. Brother _____? to Sister Mary., A.L.S.
    - 16. 1876, Oct. 3. _____(?) Unknown to Brother., A.L.
    - 17. 1876, Dec. 9.N.P. Pasquale Bresdrini to Unknown., A.L.S.
    - 18. 1876, Dec. 15.S.F., Ca. Tobin & Tobin to _____(?), Stuart & Elder., A.L.S.
    - 19. 1876, Dec. 18.S.F., Ca. R. Roy to E.W.S.*, G.P. Kellogg, Chas. Laird, W.A. Stuart., A.L.S.
    - 20. 1876, Dec. 19.S.F., Ca. Steele & Elder (A.E.) to E.W.S.*, A.L.S.
    - 21. 1876, Dec. 30. _____(?) Station. G.S. to Brother., A.L.S.
    - 22. 1877, Jan. 10.S.F., Ca. E.W.S.* to Brother re: ranching., A.L.S.
    - 23. 1877, Jan. 17.San Luis, Ca. E.W.S.* to Brother re: finances., A.L.S.
    - 24. 1877, Jan. 23.Ranch House. E.W.S.* to Brother re: finances., A.L.S.
    - 25. 1877, Jan. 24, Wednesday.N.P. Em to Isaac., A.L.S.
    - 26. 1877, Feb. 5.Tessyburg. G.S. to Brother., A.L.S.
    - 27. 1877, Feb. 8.Santa Rosa, Ca. [W.E. McConnell] to E.W.S.* re: taxes., A.L.
    - 28. 1877, Feb. 12.Ranch House. E.W.S.* to Brother re: ranching, taxes., A.L.S.
    - 29. 1877, Feb. 19.S.F., Ca. Stuart & Elder to E.W.S.*, A.L.S.
    - 30. 1877, Feb. 22.N.P. Unknown to Brother. frag., A.L.
    - 31. 1877, Feb. 28.Ranch House. E.W.S.* to Brother., A.L.S.
    - 32. 1877, Mar. 4.Knight's Valley, Sonoma Co. Knight's Valley House (E.E.) to I.C.S., A.L.S.
    - 33. 1877, May 10.S.F., Ca. Unknown to Brother., A.L.S.
    - 34. 1877, May 18.S.F., Ca. Unknown to Brother., A.L.
    - 35. 1877, May 18.S.F., Ca. E.W.S.* to Brother re: dairying., A.L.S.
    - 36. 1877, Aug. 4.S.F., [Ca.]. Unknown to Brother., A.L.S.
    - 37. 1877, Aug. 12.S.F., Ca. California Dairymens' Association (E.J.W.) to I.C.S., A.L.S.
    - 38. 1877, Aug. 15.Berkeley, Ca. Eug. W. Hilgard to I.C.S., copy.
    - 39. 1877, Aug. 25.Berlin Heights O. Hudson Tuttle to S.J. Finney., A.L.S.
    - 40. 1877, Sept. 8.S.F., Ca. E.W.S.* to Brother., A.L.S.
    - 41. 1877, Nov. 4.Sherman, Unknown to Brothers & Sisters., A.L.
    - 42. 1877, Dec. 15.Boston. A. Howe (?) to Brother & Sister., A.L.S.
    - 43. 1877, Dec. 16.E.C. Moore to Brother & Sister., A.L.S.
    - 44. 1877, Dec. 21.Point of Pimker (?). G.M.T. Carter to Steele., A.L.S.
    - 45. 1877, Dec. 25.Berlin Heights O. Hudson Tuttle to Mrs. M.B. Finney., A.L.S.
    - 46. 1877, Dec. 29.S.F., Ca. E.W.S.* to Brother re: cattle., A.L.S.
    - 47. 1877, Dec. 30.Amherst. I.C.S. to Niece., A.L.S.
    - 48. 1878, Jan. 1.Delhi. E.E. M[oore] to Brother & Sister., A.L.S.
    - 49. 1878, Jan. 4.Boston. A. Howe to Brother., A.L.S.
    - 50. 1878, Jan. 4.Pescadero, Ca. I.C.S. to Bro. Carter., A.L.S.
    - 51. 1878, Jan. 9. _____(?) Bedford. J.W. _____(?) to Mr. & Mrs. I.C.S., A.L.S.
    - 52. 1878, Feb. 4.Amherst, Unknown to Brother., A.L.S.
    - 53. 1878, June 13.Kellogg, Ca. E.W.S.* to Brother re: cattle., A.L.S.
    - 54. 1878, June 26.S.F., Ca. E.W.S.* to Brother., A.L.S.
    - 55. 1878, July 9.Kellogg, Ca. E.W.S.* to Brother re: cattle., A.L.S.
    - 56. 1878, July 15.S.F., Ca. E.W.S.* to Brother., A.L.S.
    - 57. 1878, Nov. 28.Salinas City, Ca. Salinas City Bank (A.B.J.) to Steele., A.L.S.
    - 58. 1878, Dec. 29.Sacramento, Ca. Unknown to Brother., A.L.
    - 59. 1879, April 9.S.F., Ca. Calif. Farmers' Mutual (I.G.G.) to I.C.S., A.L.S.
    - 60. 1879, Nov. 22.S.F., Ca. Steele, Elder & Co. to I.C.S. re: finances., A.L.S.
    - 61. 1879, Nov. 28.S.F., Ca. E.D. Farnsworth to I.C.S., A.L.S.
    - 62. 1879, Nov. 29.S.F., Ca. Steele, Elder & Co. to I.C.S. re: finances., A.L.S.
    - 63. 1880, _____(?) 23.Pescadero. _____(?) Wilson to I.C.S., A.L.S.
    - 64. 1880, Mar. 28.San Luis Obispo. G.S. to Brother. re: ranching., A.L.S.
    - 65. 1880, June 27.Redwood City. I.I. Cloud to I.C.S., A.L.S.
    - 66. 1880, July 25.At Home G.S. to Brother re: ranching - wheat crops., A.L.S.
    - 67. 1880, Aug. 1.San Luis Obispo. Unknown to Brother re: politics., A.L.
    - 68. 1880, Oct. 20.Pescadero, James Wilson to I.C.S., A.L.S.
    - 69. 1881, Mar. 27.S.F., Ca. Navajo Mining Co. (R.H.B.) to I.C.S., A.L.S.
    - 70. 1881, April 25.Point New Year. Unknown to Grangers (B.A.)., A.L.
    - 71. 1881, June 6.S.F., Ca. Forsaith & Dodge to I.C.S., A.L.S.
    - 72. 1881, June 14.Baker City, Oregon. R.H. Brown (?) to I.C.S., A.L.S.
    - 73. 1881, June 22.Baker City, Oregon, R.H. Brown to I.C.S., tel.
    - 74. 1881, June 22.Baker City, Oregon. R.H. Brown to I.C.S. re: Oregon stock and crops., A.L.S.
    - 75. 1881, June 24.Baker City. R.H. Brown to I.C.S., A.L.S.
    - 76. 1881, July 5.Baker City. R.H. Brown to I.C.S. re: ranching, crops, butter., A.L.S.
    - 77. 1882, May 20.S.F., Ca. R.H. R____(?) to I.C.S. re: matters of estate., A.L.S.
    - 78. 1881, July 13.Baker City, Oregon. R.H. Brown to I.C.S., A.L.S.
    - 79. 1882, Jan. 31.Santa Cruz. Wm. O. Lloyd to Mr. Steele., A.L.S.
    - 80. 1884, Aug. 13.Pescadero. C.A. Weeks to Mr. & Mrs. Steele., A.L.S.
    - 81. 1884, Nov. 5. _____(?) Louis _____(?) to Steele. in Spanish., A.L.S.
    - 82. 1886, June 10.S.F., Ca. J. Dewing & Co. to I.C.S., A.L.S.
    - 83. 1887, Aug. 3.Iowa City, Iowa. Thomas B. Wales to I.C.S., T.L.S.
    - 84. 1889, Nov. 8.Watsonville, Ca. Pajaro Valley Bank to I.C.S., A.L.S.
    - 85. 1889, Nov. 11.Oakland. _____(?) Eliot to I.C.S., A.L.S.
    - 86. 1891, Mar. 18.Pigeon Point, Ca. School Trustees to Supervisors of San Mateo County re: taxes., copy.
    - 87. 1895, July 29.Home. F.N.S. to Toes., A.L.S.
    - 88. 1896, April 29.S.F., Ca. F.W. Spencer Co. (F.W.S.) to Mrs. Ella Steele Brown., T.L.
  - Correspondence, 1900-1910 (Folder 1, Folder 5)
    - 1. 1900, June 22.Chicago. John H. Woodbury, Dermatological Institute to Mrs. F.N.S., T.L.S.
    - 2. 1900, Aug. 21.Redwood City, Ca. Joseph J. Bullock, District Attorney, San Mateo County to F.N.S. re: game hunting laws., T.L.S.
    - 3. 1900, Aug. 23.Stanford University, Ca. M.A. Clark to F.N.S., T.L.S.
    - 4. 1900, Aug. 23.Santa Clara, Ca. The League of American Sportsmen (C.B.) to F.N.S. re: quail laws.
    - 5. 1900, Aug. 29.Santa Clara, Ca. League of American Sportsmen (C.B.)
    - 6. 1902, May 27.S.F., Ca. Paraffine Paint Co. (R.S.S.) to I.C.S., T.L.S.
    - 7. 1902, Aug. 20.S.F., Ca. Paraffine Paint Co. (R.S.S.) to I.C.S., T.L.S.
    - 8. 1902, Oct. 5.Guernsey. Haw_ (?) to Steele re: farming - grape crops., A.L.S.
    - 9. 1902, Oct. 10.Santa Cruz, Ca. Henry D. Hall to Will.
    - 10. 1902, Nov. 18.S.F., Ca. Sherman, Clay & Co. to F.N.S., T.L.
    - 11. 1903, Jan. 16.S.F., Ca. San Francisco Savings Union (L.V.) to I.C.S., T.L.S.
    - 12. 1903, Feb. 16.Oakland, Ca. Robert Scofield to Will., A.L.S.
    - 13. 1903, Feb. 26.Pescadero, Ca. F.N.S. to Frank Steele., A.L.S.
    - 14. 1903, Feb. 26.Pescadero, Ca. F.N.S. to R.E.S., A.L.S.
    - 15. 1903, Feb. 26.Pescadero, Ca. F.N.S. to Eber F. Steele., A.L.S.
    - 16. 1903, Feb. 26.Pescadero, Ca. F.N.S. to J.R. Bennett., A.L.S.
    - 17. 1903, Feb. 26.Pescadero, Ca. F.N.S. to Ben Brooks., A.L.S.
    - 18. 1903, Mar. 13.Corning, Ca. Robert Scofield to Will., A.L.S.
    - 19. 1903, March 20.S.F., Ca. Paraffine Paint Co. (R.S.S.) to Unknown., T.L.S.
    - 20. 1903, April 8.S.F., Ca. Haven & Haven to F.N.S., T.L.S.
    - 21. 1903, April 21.S.F., Ca. Haven & Haven to F.N.S., T.L.S.
    - 22. 1903, June 19.S.F., Ca. Same as # 19.
    - 23. 1903, Sept. 18.S.F., Ca. H.H. Taylor to F.N.S., T.L.S.
    - 24. 1903, Sept. 21.Same as # 19.
    - 25. 1903, Nov. 4.Scranton, Pa. International Correspondence Schools (H.S.R.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 26. 1903, Nov. 10.McCloud, Ca. Robert Scofield to Will., A.L.S.
    - 27. 1903, Nov. 13.Redding, Ca. A.B. Searle to U.S. Army., A.L.S.
    - 28. 1903, Nov. 18.Copley, Ca. George Neuner Jr. to Will., A.L.S.
    - 29. 1903, Dec. 21.S.F., Ca. Haven & Haven to F.N.S., T.L.S.
    - 30. 1903, Dec. 21.Bakersfield, Ca. Mae Searle to Mrs. Steele., A.L.S.
    - 31. 1904, Feb. 17.Chicago, Ill. Gillette Sales Co. (G.A.T.) to I.C.S., T.L.S.
    - 32. 1904, Mar. 11.S.F., Ca. Haven & Haven to F.N.S., T.L.S.
    - 33. 1904, Mar. 22.Oakland, Ca. Bernard to Will., A.L.S.
    - 34. 1904, May 5.Sacramento, Ca. A.B. Searle to Will., A.L.S.
    - 35. 1904, May 12.Watsonville, Ca. Pajaro Valley Bank (J.M.) to F.N.S., T.L.S.
    - 36. 1904, May 29.Port Hill, Idaho. George Neuner Jr. to Will., A.L.S.
    - 37. 1904, July 18.Camp at Cathedral D_____(?). George Neuner Jr. to Will., A.L.S.
    - 38. 1905, Jan. 3.N.P. E.W.S.* to Cousins re: lease matters., A.L.S.
    - 39. 1905, Feb. 23.Socurro (?), New Mexico. A. Benson Searle to William., A.L.S.
    - 40. 1905, Mar. 31.S.F., Ca. Paraffine Paint Co. (R.S.S.) to F.N.S., T.L.S.
    - 41. 1905, April 11.S.F., Ca. Paraffine Paint Co. (R.S.S.) to F.N.S., T.L.S.
    - 42. 1905, June 10.Washington, D.C. Department of Interior - U.S. Geological Survey (A.B.S.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 43. 1905, June 16.Edna. A. Mason to F.N.S. re: farming., A.L.S.
    - 44. 1905, July 13.S.F., Ca. San Francisco Savings Union (R.M.W.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 45. 1907, May 25.S.F., Ca. S.F. Savings Union (R.M.W.) to F.N.S., T.L.S.
    - 46. 1907, June 3.Lakewood. Norri(?) to Chloe., A.L.S.
    - 47. 1907, Oct. 10.S.F., Ca. Grangers Bank of Calif. (S.T.M.) to Unknown., T.L.
    - 48. 1907, Oct. 24.Redwood City, Ca. 1st Nat'l. Bank of San Mateo Co. (L.P.B.) to G.H. Steele., T.L.S.
    - 49. 1908, Dec. 9.Santa Cruz, Ca. W.M. Gardner to Chloe R. Steele., T.L.S.
    - 50. 1909, May 21.Watsonville, Ca. Pajaro Valley Bank (C.A.P.) to Chloe R. Steele., T.L.S.
    - 51. 1909, July 22.Same as # 50.
    - 52. 1909, Dec. 29.Santa Cruz, Ca. Frank B. to Will., P.C.S.
    - 53. 1910, Jan. 15.Watsonville, Ca. Pajaro Valley Nat'l. Bank (J.J.M.*) to Chloe R. Steele., T.L.S.
  - Correspondence, 1916-1929 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 1. 1916, May 29.Milbrae, Ca. Milbrae Dairy (J.R.) to W.F.S. re: dairy production statistics, A.L.S.
    - 2. 1916, Nov. 19.S.F., Ca. Samuel G. Boyd, M.D. to Mrs. Steele., A.L.S.
    - 3. 1916, Nov. 20.S.F., Ca. Samuel G. Boyd, M.D. to Mrs. Steele., A.L.S.
    - 4. 1917, Sept. 29.Alpine Evaporated Cream Co. to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 5. 1918, Feb. 12.Fort Sill, Okla. Jay W. Williams to Will., A.L.S.
    - 6. 1918, Aug. 1.Woodland, Ca. J.H. Harlan Co. (C.S.) to William Steele., T.L.S.
    - 7. 1918, Aug. 29.S.F., Ca. Hibernia Savings & Loan Society (J.O.T.) to C.R.S., T.L.S.
    - 8. 1918, Oct. 6.Swanton, Ca. Emma [Steele] to Will., A.L.S.
    - 9. 1918, Oct. 9.At Home. Clara [Steele] to Will., A.L.S.
    - 10. 1918, Nov. 19.S.F., Ca. C.F. Humphrey to Unknown re: Rancho Punta Del Ano Nuevo., T.L.S.
    - 11. 1919, July 16.Swanton, Ca. C.H. Humphrey(?) to W.F.S. re: ranch business., T.L.S.
    - 12. 1920, Feb. 10.S.F., Ca. Savings Union Bank & Trust Co. (R.B.B.) to C.R.S., T.L.
    - 13. 1920, Mar. 8.S.F., Ca. Savings Union Bank & Trust Co. (W.N.F.) to Emma Steele., T.L.S.
    - 14. 1920, Mar. 8.S.F., Ca. S.U. Bk. & T. Co. (W.N.F.) to Clara Steele., T.L.S.
    - 15. 1920, Mar. 12.Redwood City, Ca. T.C. Rice (San Mateo County recorder) to W.F.S., A.L.S.
    - 16. 1920, May 7.N.P. Unknown to Redwood City Co. Clerk (E.N.), T.L.
    - 17. 1920, May 7.N.P. Unknown to County Recorder of Santa Cruz County., T.L.
    - 18. 1920, May 13.Santa Cruz, Ca. Santa Cruz Land Title Co. (H.S.G.) to C.F. Humphrey., T.L.S.
    - 19. 1920, June 19.N.P. Unknown to Redwood City County Clerk (E.N.)., T.L.
    - 20. 1920, June 20.Redwood City, Ca. Times-Gazette (D.E.O.) to C.F. Humphrey., T.L.S.
    - 21. 1920, Aug. 16.N.P. Unknown to W.F.S., T.L.
    - 22. 1920, Oct. 2.N.P. Unknown to Redwood City Co. Clerk (E.N.)., T.L.
    - 23. 1920, Oct. 12.N.P. Unknown to Redwood City Co. Clerk (E.N.)., T.L.
    - 24. 1920, Dec. 9.Swanton, Ca. C.H. Humphrey to W.F.S. re: ranch finances., T.L.S.
    - 25. 1921, April 8.N.P. C.F. H[umphrey] to Redwood City Co. Clerk (E.N.), T.L.
    - 26. 1921, May 27.N.P. Unknown to Elizabeth Nash, Redwood City County Clerk re: estates of Clara and Emma Steele., T.L.
    - 27. 1921, May 27.S.F., Ca. C.F. Humphrey to Redwood City Co. Clerk (E.N.)., T.L.S.
    - 28. 1921, Dec. 8.S.F., Ca. Mercantile Trust Co. (R.R.B.) to C.R.S., T.L.S.
    - 29. 1922, Feb. 9.At Home. Mother to Will., A.L.S.
    - 30. 1922, Oct. 12.N.P. R.E. to W.S.
    - 31. 1923, June 28.Santa Cruz, Ca. W. Grant Hatch, M.D. to C.R.S., T.L.S.
    - 32. 1923, Nov. 17.Sacramento, Ca. Tibbals & Percival (C.L.T.) to C.F. Humphrey., T.L.S.
    - 33. 1923, Dec. 12.S.F., Ca. Western Meat Co. (S.B.C.) to W.F.S. re: dairy product - cream., T.L.S.
    - 34. 1924, Oct. 24.Houston, Texas. Southern Pacific Lines (E.J.P.) to W.C. McCormick., T.L.